### PERFORMANCE PROFILE

Designer and developer with a lot of teamwork and leadership experience. Ability to plan and understand project requirements and structure and design them efficiently. Extensive frontend experience with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Currently delving into backend with Node.js, Express, and MongoDB. Exploring JS frameworks, including React and Angular. Fluent in Visual Studio Code, Adobe Creative Cloud software.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### FREELANCE DESIGNER / DEVELOPER NICK BRAVO.DEV / 2007 - PRESENT

- Build private and secure websites, portals, visual identities, and online assets to solidify brand authority and trust across platforms.
- Design digital graphics using Adobe Creative Cloud Software.
- Work with clients to achieve desired look, feel, and outcome.

# **GRAPHIC DESIGNER / WEB DEVELOPER**

### 8FISH / 2008 - 2009

- Worked with clients to develop brand identities, web and print graphics, websites, and other digital media assets to reinforce and elevate brands.
- Created artwork and illustrations for print and web.
- Crafted and managed social media and digital marketing content.

#### POLICE OFFICER

#### POLICE DEPARTMENT / 2021 - PRESENT

- Acted as liaison between police department and marketing department to generate positive educational safety content for students, faculty, and staff.
- Participated in content planning for a safety app currently in development.

#### **POLICE DETECTIVE**

#### POLICE DEPARTMENT / 2015 - 2021

- Developed and supervised a comprehensive firearm deployment and training program.
- Engaged in community events and public outreach programs, including D.A.R.E.
- Investigated crimes, interviewed suspects, responded to citizen complaints, and positively interacted with people in crisis.

#### **POLICE LIEUTENANT**

#### POLICE DEPARTMENT / 2010 - 2015

- Designed and developed department website and managed social media.
- Drafted press releases for media outlets.
- Participated in community events to build trust with the community.
- Interfaced with other public safety agencies to improve service quality.
- Developed Reserve Officer program that slashed personnel budget by 30%.
- Quarterbacked operations, training, and budget.

# **EDUCATION**

**BACHELOR OF SCIENCE / DIGITAL CINEMATOGRAPHY** UNIVERSITY / NOV 2019

**GPA 3.99 / VALEDICTORIAN** 

ASSOCIATE OF APPLIED SCIENCE / GRAPHIC DESIGN COLLEGE OF MAY 2008

# HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- **JavaScript**
- Node.is
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Visual Studio Code
- Adobe Creative Suite

### SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- **Decision Making**
- Team Leadership
- **Public Relations**
- Strategic Planning
- Interpersonal Communication
- Crisis Intervention
- Conflict Resolution
- Critical Thinking
- **Detail Oriented**
- Presentations